{
    "subject": "resource/Caught_in_the_Rain",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "Caught in the Rain  is a 1914 American comedy silent film starring Charlie Chaplin. This film was the first of many movies in which Chaplin both directed and played the lead. The short film was produced by Mack Sennett for Keystone Studios with a running time of 16 minutes.",
    "human_readable": "Caught in the Rain is a 1914 American comedy silent film starring Charlie Chaplin, which was the first of many movies where Chaplin both directed and played the lead.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9447004199028015,
            "question": "Was Charlie Chaplin involved in directing 'Caught in the Rain'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9172252416610718,
            "question": "Is 'Caught in the Rain' considered a significant film in Charlie Chaplin's career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9105725884437561,
            "question": "Who starred in the silent film 'Caught in the Rain'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9013122916221619,
            "question": "Did Charlie Chaplin also play a role in 'Caught in the Rain'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8361757397651672,
            "question": "Besides acting, what other role did Charlie Chaplin have in 'Caught in the Rain'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7652120590209961,
            "question": "What type of film was 'Caught in the Rain'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7292993664741516,
            "question": "What genre was the film 'Caught in the Rain'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.718808650970459,
            "question": "Was 'Caught in the Rain' a successful film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7176578044891357,
            "question": "What year was the film 'Caught in the Rain' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.705436110496521,
            "question": "What was special about 'Caught in the Rain' in relation to Charlie Chaplin's work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Caught in the Rain is a 1914 American comedy silent film starring Charlie Chaplin, which was the first of many movies where Chaplin both directed and played the lead.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3472_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was the film 'Caught in the Rain' released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3472_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was 'Caught in the Rain' a successful film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3472_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre was the film 'Caught in the Rain'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3472_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3472_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3472_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3472_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3472_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3472_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3472_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3472_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3472_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3472_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3472_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The documents state that \"Caught in the Rain\" is a 1914 American comedy silent film starring Charlie Chaplin, and that it was his first film where he both directed and played the lead."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports this triple. The details in files `7.txt`, `22.txt`, and `27.txt` confirm that \"Caught in the Rain\" is a 1914 American comedy silent film starring Charlie Chaplin, and it was one of his earliest films where he both directed and played the lead role."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}